<?xml version="1.0"?>
<catalog>
   <book id="bk101">
      <episode>Episode 1</episode>
      <title>Wolf Moon</title>
      <description>An unusual occurrence while searching for a missing body in the woods 
      with his best friend gives sophomore Scott McCall everything he'd ever wanted:
       new lacrosse abilities, a date with the girl of his dreams, and supernatural skills.
        But is there a downside to these new powers</description>
        <link>fetch.html</link>
   </book>
   <book id="bk102">
       <episode>Episode 2</episode>
      <title>Second Chance 
      at First line</title>
      <description>Scott tries to control his new werewolf powers, and faces mounting pressure from
       friends (including new love interest, Allison) and family alike to play in the coming 
       lacrosse game. Can he stop his transformation before it's too late?</description>
        <link>fetch.html</link>
   </book>
   <book id="bk103">
       <episode>Episode 3</episode>
      <title>Pack Mentality</title>
      <description>Scott is shaken when a nightmare coincides uncannily with the mauling of a school
       bus driver, an attack that puts Sheriff Stilinski and the rest of Beacon Hills on high alert.
        Meanwhile, Scott is excited for his first date with Allison, until it becomes a confusing
         group date with Lydia and Jackson to the bowling alley</description>
         <link>fetch.html</link>
  
   </book>
   <book id="bk104">
      <episode>Episode 4</episode>
      <title>Magic Bullet</title>
      <description>Kate Argent, Allison's aunt, arrives in town and is attacked by the Alpha. 
      While fighting it off, she shoots Derek. Now, Scott has to make it through an awkward family 
      dinner with the Argents to get a bullet to save him, while Stiles and Derek attempt to slow
       the effects of the wound.</description>
  <link>fetch.html</link>
   </book>
   <book id="bk105">
   <episode>Episode 5</episode>
      <title>The tell</title>
      <description>Lydia and Jackson witness an animal attack at the video store. Kate gives Allison
       a family heirloom and encourages her to use it to learn more about the family history.
        Meanwhile, Derek must deal with the werewolf hunters on his own. Scott and Allison skip school,
         but are soon caught by their families at parent-teacher conferences</description>
  <link>fetch.html</link>
   </book>
   <book id="bk106">
     <episode>Episode 6</episode>
      <title>Heart Monitor</title>
      <description>Scott attempts to control his anger and transformation so he can spend more time 
      with Allison, assisted by Stiles and a heart monitor. Derek continues trying to make an ally 
      of Scott in order to defeat the Alpha, and Jackson is feeling the effects of having been 
      scratched.</description>
      <link>fetch.html</link>
   </book>
   <book id="bk107">
<episode>Episode 7</episode>
      <title>Night School</title>
      <description>Responding to Scott's howl, the alpha savages Derek and traps Scott and Stiles
       in their high school. Events escalate even further when Allison, Jackson and Lydia are lured
        to the school as well with a phony text message. At the end of the night, 
        Allison breaks up with Scott after saying she cannot trust him</description>
        <link>fetch.html</link>
   </book>
   <book id="bk108">
     <episode>Episode 8</episode>
      <title>Lunatic</title>
      <description>As Scott's second full moon approaches, he gives in to his animal urges and hurts
       Stiles, but Stiles gets a measure of revenge in locking him up. Meanwhile, Jackson continues
        to try to get closer to Allison. The Argents learn that Scott somehow knew Derek.</description>
        <link>fetch.html</link>
   </book>
   <book id="bk109">
      <episode>Episode 9</episode>
      <title>Wolf's bane</title>
      <description>Jackson discovers that he has aconite poisoning and thinks he has figured out what is 
      up with Scott. Meanwhile, Derek hides from the manhunt in Stiles' room while Stiles and Scott try 
      to get Allison's necklace and any clues that may lead to the identity of the alpha. 
      Teammate Danny lends Stiles his internet expertise to help in the search. 
      Derek and Stiles discover the identity of the Alpha.</description>
      <link>fetch.html</link>
   </book>
   <book id="bk110">
     <episode>Episode 10</episode>
      <title>Co captain</title>
      <description>The Alpha finally reveals himself to Scott who happens to be Peter, Derek's uncle and gives
       him an idea of why he has killed certain people. Argent stages an encounter thinking that
        Jackson may be a werewolf. Meanwhile, Allison discovers a bit more about her
         family's secrets and confronts Lydia about her kissing Scott</description>
         <link>fetch.html</link>
         
   </book>
   <book id="bk111">
      <episode>Episode 11</episode>
      <title>Formality</title>
      <description>Kate has Derek chained up in a basement following her attack on his house and shows him 
      off to Allison before torturing him. The coach has banned Scott from the Spring Formal in exchange for
       not dropping him from the team for academic 
      reasons</description>
      <link>fetch.html</link>
   </book>
   <book id="bk112">
     <episode>Episode 12</episode>
      <title>Code Breaker</title>
      <description>Argent decides to send Allison and his sister Kate to Washington. Stiles helps Peter 
      locate Derek. Meanwhile,Jackson is called to get Lydia to the hospital. Scott must cope with the
       girl he loves knowing his secret. Argent and the  hunters try to get Scott's location out of Stiles
        and Jackson.</description>
        <link>fetch.html</link>
   </book>
</catalog>